import '../Models/quiz.dart';

const List<Quiz> quizList = [
  Quiz(
    questionText: "1 + 1?",
    options: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "1 + 5?",
    options: ['7', '1', '5', '6'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "5 - 5?",
    options: ['-5', '5', '0', '1'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "12 - 2?",
    options: ['9', '8', '0', '10'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "4 x 8?",
    options: ['32', '48', '24', '12'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "9 x 8?",
    options: ['64', '72', '56', '81'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "22 / 7 ?",
    options: ['4', '13.8', '3.14', '7.21'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "51 / 17?",
    options: ['2.8', '2.4', '3', '4'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "4 + 17 x 2?",
    options: ['51', '42', '38', '58'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "7 x 8 / 5?",
    options: ['11.2', '10.2', '12', '11.5'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "6 x 7 x 2?",
    options: ['84', '96', '72', '82'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "81 / 9 + 2 x 9?",
    options: ['9', '99', '3', '27'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "8 ... 9 ... 4 = 44",
    options: ['x dan x', '+ dan x', 'x dan +', 'x dan -'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "jawabannya B",
    options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  ),Quiz(
    questionText: "jawaban dari soal nomor  8?",
    options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  ),
];